infanion.com 2013-07-24

# Privacy policy | Infanion

Infanion is committed to safeguard your privacy online. Infanion collects and stores the details that you voluntarily provide on this website or that you voluntarily provide to our customer services. These details are used in order to supply the information requested and to facilitate customer service. The information may also be used to approach you concerning special offers and any new functionality on this website. Your personal data is never used for secondary or unrelated purposes unless otherwise requested or explicitly agreed by you. We do not collect and store any personal details concerning your physical/mental health, memberships, race or ethnic origin, political convictions, religion or other belief, sex life or criminal record. We may automatically collect and store certain other details when you visit this site. For example, every time you visit this website we may store your IP address, browser information and the domain name of the reference site. We also collect information on visitor patterns and site usage. This information is used to evaluate the site and to improve it for purposes of providing our visitors and customers with a satisfying experience. In common with many other websites, we also use cookies (small files that are stored on the hard disk of your computer by your browser). Cookies help us to recognise visitors and to improve their visiting experience.

The website of Infanion may contain links to the websites of third parties. Bear in mind that the guidelines described in this privacy policy do not apply to information collected via other websites. We therefore advise you to read the privacy policy of each website you visit. If you have gained access to this website via a link from certain of our advertising or marketing partners, the pages may be in the context of the relevant advertisement or marketing partner. Nevertheless, we collect the details that you provide on these pages and this privacy policy applies to those details.

What about online questionnaires? From time to time, we may hold online questionnaires. If you participate in an online questionnaire, we may ask you for certain information, such as your age, postcode, shopping behaviour, e-mail address and/or postal address. Such information is treated in accordance with this privacy policy.

In the event of changes to this privacy policy, we will place a message on the website to inform users of them. In some cases, we may send an e-mail to inform users. We advise you to check the website regularly for any changes to the privacy policy.

If you wish to contact us with regards to the Infanion privacy policy, you may do so

  * Via e-mail: [info@infanion.com](mailto:info@infanion.com)
  * By telephone: + 32 3 369 01 66  (Monday-Friday between 10h & 12h and between 14h & 16h)
  * By fax: + 32 3 369 01 69
  * By mail: Infanion, Van de Wervestraat 8, 2060 Antwerpen, Belgium
